(Amy:)-Do you hear anything?
-I hear a woman's voice.
(Amy:)-Is it Penny?
-No, it's you.
(Stuart:)All right,
I hearwhispering and giggling.
(Sheldon:)Now I think I hear kissing.
(Amy:)Yeah, like you know
what kissing sounds like.
(Sheldon:)There's kissing in Star Trek,
smarty-pants.
(Amy:)Let me listen.
(Amy:)-Sounds like Leonard.
-Please.
(Sheldon:)Why would Leonard come home early
and waste his time kissing Penny
(Sheldon:)when he could be hanging out
with his best buddy?
(Sheldon:)Yeah, that's it.
I'm catching her in the act.
(Amy:)No, Sheldon, don't.
A-ha!
-What the hell?!
-Leonard?
(Penny:)Sheldon, you cannot just
barge in here like that!
(Stuart:)Right.
Penny! Penny! Penny!
(Sheldon:)Are you going to answer the door
or should I open it